Register of the Finnish Relief Fund records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Publicity Division File, 1939-1946
  Memoranda, press releases, press statements, radiobroadcast transcripts, reports, pamphlets, programs of events, and publications, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Background material for International Year Book, 1941 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Blue slip "Help Finland" (Folder 2)
  - Booklet Helping Finland (Folder 3)
  - Books (Folder 4)
  - Buttons (Folder 5)
  - Clippings re Finland
    - General, 1940-1941 (Folder 6)
    - Russo-Finnish War
      - 1939 December (Folder 7)
      - 1940
        - January-February (Folder 8)
        - March-April (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University Press publications (Folder 2)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - A-F (Folder 3)
      - G-Q (Folder 4)
      - R-Z (Folder 5)
    - Wright, W. (Folder 6)
  - Match boxes (Folder 7)
  - Memoranda, especially of James Selvage, director of division (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Pictures and paintings (Folder 2)
  - Poems (Folder 3)
  - Postage stamp "Help Finland Stamp"
    - Correspondence (Folder 4)
    - Desk file of Perrin Galpin (Folder 5)
    - Sales figures (Folder 6)
  - Postal issues of Finland (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Posters (Folder 2)
  - Press releases
    - General (Folder 3)
    - First set
      - 1939
        - (#1-50), December 7 -December 19 (Folder 4)
        - (#51-100), December 19 -December 22 (Folder 5)
      - (#101-150), 1939 December 23-1940 January 4 (Folder 6)
      - 1940
        - (#151-200), January 5 -January 18 (Folder 7)
        - (#201-235), January 19 -February 21 (Folder 8)
    - Second set (Box 56)
      - 1939 December (Folder 1)
      - 1940
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February-May (Folder 3)
  - Publications (Box 57)
    - The Betrayal of Finland: A Phantasy by Philip J. Webster (Folder 1)
    - Finland and Russia: Historical and Social Background of the War by Kyosti Haataya (Folder 2)
    - Finland's Struggle for Freedom (Folder 3)
    - Post-War Reconstruction (rehousing research in Finland by Alvar Aalto) (Folder 4)
    - Where is the Soul of America?: Born through a "Foreign Alliance" America Hesitates to Support Finland (Folder 5)
    - Help Finland (foreword written by Herbert Hoover) (Folder 6)
    - First Finnish Settlement in America, 1638: 300th Anniversary Celebration, Official program, Chester, Pennsylvania, 1938 June 29 (Folder 7)
    - For Western Civilization, 1939 December (Folder 8)
    - Helping Finland, Address, Madison Square Garden, New York, 1939 December 20 (Folder 9)
    - Finnish Relief Fund: Provisional Organization as of January 1, 1940, 1940 January 2 (Folder 10)
    - Suggested Outline of Procedure in Organizing Committees to Cooperate with the Finnish Relief Fund, Inc., 1940 January 8 (Folder 11)
    - Finnish Relief Fund: Provisional organization as of January 10, 1940 (Folder 12)
    - Kohler of Kohler News, Published monthly at Kohler, Wisconsin, by and for the Kohler Co. Organization, 1940 February (Folder 13)
    - Two Letters, 1940 February (Folder 14)
    - Finnish Relief Fund. National Organization as of February 24, 1940 (Folder 15)
    - "A Bulletin to Help the Intelligent Citizen Detect and Analyze Propaganda," Propaganda Analysis, Printed by the Institute for Propaganda Analysis, Inc., New York City, 1940 April (Folder 16)
    - Letter from Finland (in which the Red Cross thanks Great Britain for relaxing the blockade on Finland), 1941 March (Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 18)
  - Radiobroadcast/transcripts (Folder 19)
  - Reports
    - General
      - Final (Folder 20)
      - To American donors (Folder 21)
      - Of the FRF Health Commission (Folder 22)
      - On the activities of the Mannerheim League (Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Slogan (Folder 2)
  - Songs (Folder 3)
  - Stamp "Help Finland" (Folder 4)
  - Statements to the press (Folder 5)
  - Subject file
    - Divisions
      - Collection Box (Folder 6)
      - Industrial (Folder 7)
      - Motion Picture (Folder 8)
      - Music and Entertainment (Folder 9)
      - Theatrical (Folder 10)
      - Women's (Folder 11)
    - Eastern Office (Folder 12)
    - Legal Department (Folder 13)
    - Lincoln Day Dinner (Folder 14)
    - Newspapers
      - Advertising file (Folder 15)
      - Clippings, 1939-1946 (Box 59-64)
      - Contributions received (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence
        - Alabama-Arkansas (Folder 2-4)
        - California
          - A-B (Folder 5)
          - C-E (Folder 6)
          - G-I (Folder 7)
          - L (Folder 8)
          - M-O (Folder 9)
          - P-Q (Box 66, Folder 1)
          - S
            - General (Folder 2)
            - San Diego (Folder 3)
            - San Francisco (Folder 4)
          - T-Y (Folder 5)
        - Colorado (Folder 6)
        - Connecticut
          - B-G (Folder 7)
          - H (Folder 8)
          - L-M (Box 67, Folder 1)
          - N (Folder 2)
          - R-S (Folder 3)
          - T-W (Folder 4)
        - District of Columbia (Folder 5)
        - Florida
        - Georgia-Idaho
        - Illinois (Folder 8-9)
        - Indiana (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - Iowa (Folder 2)
        - Kansas (Folder 3-4)
        - Kentucky-Louisiana (Folder 5)
        - Maine (Folder 6)
        - Maryland (Folder 7)
        - Massachusetts (Folder 8-9)
        - Michigan (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
        - Minnesota (Folder 3-4)
        - Mississippi (Folder 5)
        - Missouri (Folder 6)
        - Montana (Folder 7)
        - Nebraska (Folder 8)
        - Nevada (Folder 9)
        - New Hampshire (Box 70, Folder 1)
        - New Jersey (Folder 2-4)
        - New Mexico (Folder 5)
        - New York (Box 71)
          - General (Folder 1-6)
          - General (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
          - General (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
          - Brooklyn (Folder 3-6)
        - North Carolina (Box 74, Folder 1)
        - North Dakota (Folder 2)
        - Ohio (Folder 3-4)
        - Oklahoma (Folder 5)
        - Oregon (Folder 6-7)
        - Pennsylvania (Box 75, Folder 1-5)
        - Rhode Island (Box 76, Folder 1)
        - South Carolina (Folder 2)
        - South Dakota (Folder 3)
        - Tennessee (Folder 4)
        - Texas (Folder 5-6)
        - Utah (Folder 7)
        - Vermont (Box 77, Folder 1)
        - Virginia (Folder 2)
        - Washington (Folder 3-4)
        - West Virginia (Folder 5)
        - Wisconsin (Folder 6)
        - Wyoming (Folder 7)
      - Donations received (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Lost of newspapers (Folder 2)
      - Memoranda, Inter-office (Folder 3)
      - Telegrams (Folder 4-5)
    - Posters
      - Correspondence (Folder 6)
      - Mailing lists (Folder 7)
    - Statistical Department (Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 9)
- Speakers Bureau File, 1939-1940
  Correspondence and lists of engagements, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Biographies (Folder 2)
  - Correspondence
    - Bernadotte, Folke (Folder 3)
    - Brandstrom, Elsa (Folder 4)
    - Donaldson, Arthur (Folder 5)
    - Falnes, O. J. (Folder 6)
    - Hedberg, Anders (Folder 7)
    - Hoff, Trygve (Folder 8)
    - Kjelsberg, Betzy (Folder 9)
    - Lawson, Evald B. (Folder 10)
    - Michaelis, Karin (Folder 11)
    - Munyhe, Gustaf (Folder 12)
    - Nansen, Odd (Folder 13)
    - Sawders, James (Folder 14)
    - Sparre, Eva (Folder 15)
    - Sparre, Louis (Folder 16)
    - Steeholm, Hardy (Folder 17)
    - Tollet, Karin (Folder 18)
    - Tollet, Marcus (Folder 19)
    - Von Essen, George (Folder 20)
  - Lists of engagements (Folder 21)
  - Requests (Folder 22)
  - Schedules of speakers (Folder 23)
  - Subject file - Rotary clubs
    - General (Folder 24)
    - Acceptances (Folder 25)
    - Refusals (Folder 26)
- Special Events File, 1939-1941
  Mostly correspondence relating to FRF fundraising activity, arranged alphabetically by subject
  - General (Box 80)
    - General. Includes calendar of events (Folder 1)
    - Auction, New York City (Folder 2)
    - Benefits
      - "Gold Spring Festival," New York City, 1940 January 6 (Folder 3)
      - Waldorf Astoria Hotel, 1940 February 7 (Folder 4)
    - Collection boxes (Folder 5)
    - Concerts
      - General
        - New Rochelle, NY (Folder 6)
        - New York City, NY (Elmira College) (Folder 7)
        - Plainfield, NJ (Folder 8)
        - Princeton, NJ (Folder 9)
      - Haitto, Heimo (violinist)
        - General (Folder 10)
        - Biographical note and legal documents (Folder 11)
        - Concert schedule (Folder 12)
        - Correspondence
          - Finland. Consulate General (New York) and Finland. Legation (United States) (Folder 13)
          - Pickernell, Harriet Steel (Folder 14)
          - Sirpo, Boris (Folder 15)
        - Financial documents (Folder 16)
        - Statement regarding Mrs. Heimo Haitto (Folder 17)
      - Luoma, Reino (pianist) (Folder 18)
      - Soderhjlm, Ester Merte (pianist) (Folder 19)
      - Toscanini, Arturo (Folder 20)
    - Dances (Folder 21)
    - Fundraising (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Games (Folder 2)
    - Horse shows (Folder 3)
    - Ice carnival (Folder 4)
    - Lectures (Folder 5)
    - Lottery (Folder 6)
    - Lunches (Folder 7)
    - Musical, Scarsdale, NY (Folder 8)
    - Sporting events
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Ski party (Folder 10)
      - Tennis match, New York City, 1940 March 10 (Folder 11)
    - Theater (Folder 12)
  - American Legion Minstrel Show (Folder 13)
  - Boosters Club dinner (Folder 14)
  - Bridge to Finland Committee (Folder 15)
  - "Help Finland Cabaret," World's Championship (Folder 16)
  - Laulo-Miehet Finnish Male Chorus (Folder 17)
  - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra (Folder 18)
  - Madison Square Garden World's Championship (Folder 20)
  - Movie Days (Folder 21)
  - "Murmi-Maki" (Finnish runners) (Folder 22)
  - Yale Glee Club
    - Carnegie Hall, New York City (Folder 23)
    - New Haven, CT (Folder 24)
  - Yorkville Casino, New York City (Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous. Includes invitations, programs and tickets for special events (Folder 26)
- Special Projects File, 1939-1940
  Correspondence, mailing lists, receipts, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Buttons (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Coin boxes. See Coin Boxes Division File
  - Match boxes
    - Correspondence
      - General (Folder 2)
      - Unit Match Corporation (Folder 3)
    - Mailing lists (Folder 5-7)
    - Receipts
    - Receipts (Box 83, Folder 1-5)
- Coin Boxes Division File, 1939-1940
  Correspondence, lists, reports, requests, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General (Box 84)
    - Organized by collecting agency
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Banks (Folder 2)
      - Drug store chains (Folder 3)
      - Food store chains (Folder 4)
      - Montgomery Ward (Folder 5)
      - Railroad companies (Folder 6)
      - Theaters (Folder 7)
    - Organized geographically
      - Atlantic seaboard (Folder 8)
      - Midwest (Folder 9-10)
      - New England (Folder 11)
      - Pacific (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - South (Folder 2)
    - Unaccounted for
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Mailing list (Folder 4)
  - Form letters (Folder 5)
  - Lists of addresses where coin boxes are to be sent from
    - Office (Folder 6)
    - Printer (Folder 7)
  - Reports
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Structure and organization of the division (Folder 9)
  - Requests for boxes
    - American Scandinavian Division (Folder 10)
    - Industrial Division (Folder 11)
- Civic Service Organization Committee File, 1940
  Program, telegrams, letters, invitations, lists, minutes of meetings, memoranda, publicity material, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
  - Acceptances of invitations to serve on the committee (Folder 3-4)
  - Acknowledgments of contributions (Folder 5)
  - Appeals (Folder 6)
  - Correspondence. Includes correspondence of James McLean
    - A (Folder 7)
    - B (Folder 8)
    - C-D
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Chambers of commerce (Box 87, Folder 1-2)
    - I (Folder 3)
    - J-K (Folder 4)
    - L-M (Folder 5)
    - N (Folder 6)
    - O-P (Folder 7)
    - S
      - General (Folder 8-11)
      - General (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
      - State chairmen (Folder 3)
    - U-W (Folder 4)
  - Form letters sent to heads of organizations (Folder 5)
  - Invitations to become members of the National Civic Service Organizations Committee for the FRF (Folder 6)
  - Lists of organizations contacted (Folder 7)
  - Minutes of meetings with liaison officers (Folder 8)
  - Memoranda, Office (Folder 9)
  - Program of James N. McLean, chairman (Folder 10)
  - Publicity material (Folder 11)
  - Refusals (Folder 12)
  - Telegrams (Folder 13)
- Financial Records File, 1939-1947
  Accounts, audits, bills, bonds, checks, dollar transfer requests, financial statements, insurance records, receipts, correspondence, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General (Box 89-129)
  - Accounts (Box 130)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - Overhead, Contributions for (Folder 2)
    - Special events (Folder 3)
    - Withdrawals against expenses (Folder 4)
  - Audits (Folder 5)
  - Bills (Folder 6)
  - Bonds
    - Brown, Crosby and Co. (Folder 7)
    - Helsinki (Finland) (Folder 8)
    - U.S. Treasury % (safe deposit box), 2/2 (Folder 9)
  - Budget figures (Folder 10)
  - Checks (Folder 11)
  - Dollar transfer requests (Folder 12)
  - Financial statements (Folder 13)
  - Insurance records (Folder 14)
  - Receipts
    - And disbursements, 1939 December 5-1940 October 19 (Folder 15)
    - And remittances for FRF as shown by general ledger (Folder 16)
    - Used in acknowledging contributions (Folder 17)
  - Remittance Division file (Box 131)
    - General
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Remittances for arms
        - In abeyance (Folder 2)
        - Received from newspapers (Folder 3)
        - Total received (Folder 4)
    - Accounts
      - Chase National Bank (Folder 5)
      - Federal Reserve Bank (Folder 6)
      - Irving Trust Company (Folder 7)
    - Cables (Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with IRS (Folder 9)
    - Inquiry (Folder 10)
    - Statement of Herbert Hoover (Folder 11)
  - Subject file. Addresses, correspondence, memoranda, money orders
    - American Bank Note Company (Folder 12)
    - American Express Company (Folder 13)
    - Bankers Association (Folder 14)
    - Deloitte, Plender, Griffith and Company (Folder 15)
- Contributions File, 1939-1940
  Acknowledgements, checks, memoranda, receipts, reports, tabulation sheets relating mostly to donations from the United States as well as from foreign countries, arranged alphabetically by subject and geographical area
  - General (Box 132)
    - General
      - General (Folder 1-2)
      - Incomplete (Folder 3)
      - Returned (Folder 4)
    - Acknowledgments
      - General
        - General (Folder 5)
        - A (Folder 6)
        - B (Folder 7)
        - C (Folder 8)
        - D-E (Folder 9)
        - F-G (Folder 10)
        - H (Folder 11)
        - I-J (Box 133, Folder 1)
        - K-L (Folder 2)
        - Mc-Mac (Folder 3)
        - M (Folder 4)
        - N-O (Folder 5)
        - P-R (Folder 6)
        - S (Folder 7)
        - T-V (Folder 8)
        - W-Z (Folder 9)
      - American Red Cross (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Banks (Folder 2)
      - Churches
        - A-B (Folder 3)
        - C-E (Folder 4)
        - F (Folder 5)
        - G-O (Folder 6)
        - P-Z (Folder 7)
      - Clubs
        - A-B (Folder 8)
        - C-F (Folder 9)
        - G-J (Box 135, Folder 1)
        - K-Q (Folder 2)
        - R (Folder 3)
        - S-V (Folder 4)
        - W-Z (Folder 5)
      - Foundations (Folder 6-7)
      - Hotels (Folder 8)
      - Jewish organizations (Folder 9)
      - Maurice Pieters Appeal (Folder 10-11)
      - National Council of Women (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Nurses (Folder 2)
      - Schools (Folder 3)
      - Sport organizations (Folder 4)
      - Theaters (Folder 5)
      - Universities and colleges
        - General (Folder 6)
        - California (Folder 7)
        - Colorado (Folder 8)
        - Connecticut (Folder 9)
        - Florida (Folder 10)
        - Illinois-Iowa (Folder 11)
        - Kansas (Folder 12)
        - Maine (Folder 13)
        - Massachusetts (Folder 14)
        - Michigan-New Jersey (Folder 15)
        - New York-West Virginia (Folder 16)
    - Checks (Folder 17)
    - Checks (Box 137, Folder 1-2)
    - Memoranda (Folder 3-4)
    - Receipts (Folder 5)
    - Reports on collections
      - 1939 December (Folder 6)
      - 1940
        - January (Folder 7-10)
        - February (Box 138, Folder 1-4)
        - March (Folder 5-9)
        - April (Folder 10-12)
        - May (Folder 13)
    - Tabulation code (IBM) (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Tabulation sheets arranged chronologically and by industry, business, organization, or individual contributor (Folder 2-7)
    - Tabulation sheets arranged chronologically and by industry, business, organization, or individual contributor (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
  - Bermuda (Folder 4)
  - Canada (Folder 5)
  - Central and South America (Folder 6)
  - Cuba (Folder 7)
  - Dominican Republic (Folder 8)
  - Egypt (Folder 9)
  - Mexico (Folder 10)
  - Panama (Folder 11)
  - Philippines Islands (Folder 12)
  - Trinidad (Folder 13)
  - United States
    - Anonymous (Folder 14)
    - Alabama
      - General (Folder 15)
      - Anonymous (Folder 16)
      - State organization (Folder 17)
    - Alaska
      - General (Folder 18)
      - State organization (Folder 19)
    - Arizona
      - General (Folder 20)
      - Anonymous (Folder 21)
      - State organization (Folder 22)
    - Arkansas (Box 141)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Anonymous (Folder 2)
      - State organization (Folder 3)
    - California
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Anonymous (Folder 5)
      - Cities
        - Hollywood (Folder 6)
        - Los Angeles (Folder 7)
        - Oakland (Folder 8)
        - Palo Alto (Folder 9)
        - Pasadena (Folder 10)
        - San Diego (Folder 11)
        - San Francisco (Folder 12)
        - San Jose (Folder 13)
      - Individuals
        - A-L (Folder 14)
        - M-Z (Folder 15)
      - State committee - Allen, Victoria French (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - State organization (Folder 2)
    - Colorado
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Cities - Denver (Folder 4)
      - State organization (Folder 5)
    - Connecticut
      - Anonymous (Folder 6)
      - Cities
        - Bridgeport (Folder 7)
        - Darien (Folder 8)
        - Fairfield (Folder 9)
        - Greenwich (Folder 10)
        - Hartford (Folder 11)
        - New Cannon (Folder 12)
        - New Haven (Folder 13)
        - Norwalk (Folder 14)
        - Southport (Box 143, Folder 1)
        - Stamford (Folder 2)
        - Waterbury (Folder 3)
        - Westport (Folder 4)
      - Individuals (Folder 5-7)
      - State organization (Folder 8)
    - Delaware
      - General (Folder 9)
      - State organization (Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia
      - Anonymous (Folder 11)
      - Finland House (clothing) (Folder 12)
      - Individuals
        - A-C (Folder 13)
        - D-N (Box 144, Folder 1)
        - O-Z (Folder 2)
      - State organization (Folder 3)
    - Florida
      - Anonymous (Folder 4)
      - Cities
        - Daytona Beach (Folder 5)
        - Jacksonville (Folder 6)
        - Miami (Folder 7)
        - St. Petersburg (Folder 8)
        - Winter Park (Folder 9)
      - Individuals
        - A-J (Folder 10)
        - K-O (Folder 11)
        - P-Z (Folder 12)
      - State organization (Folder 13)
    - Georgia (Box 145)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - State organization (Folder 2)
    - Hawaii (Folder 3)
    - Idaho
      - General (Folder 4)
      - State organization (Folder 5)
    - Illinois
      - Anonymous (Folder 6)
      - Cities - Chicago
        - A-H (Folder 7)
        - I-Z (Folder 8)
      - Individuals
        - A-L (Folder 9)
        - M-Z (Folder 10)
      - State organization (Folder 11)
    - Indiana (Box 146)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - State organization (Folder 2)
    - Iowa
      - General (Folder 3)
      - State organization (Folder 4)
    - Kansas
      - General (Folder 5)
      - State organization (Folder 6)
    - Kentucky
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Cities - Louisville (Folder 8)
      - State organization (Folder 9)
    - Louisiana
      - General (Folder 10)
      - State organization (Folder 11)
    - Maine
      - General (Folder 12)
      - Anonymous (Folder 13)
      - State organization (Folder 14)
    - Maryland (Box 147)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Anonymous (Folder 2)
      - Cities - Baltimore (Folder 3)
      - State organization (Folder 4)
    - Massachusetts
      - Anonymous (Folder 5)
      - Cities
        - Boston
          - A-F (Folder 6)
          - G-L (Folder 7)
          - M-R (Folder 8)
          - S-Z (Folder 9)
        - Brookline (Folder 10)
        - Cambridge (Folder 11)
        - Milton (Box 148, Folder 1)
        - Springfield (Folder 2)
        - Wellesley Hills (Folder 3)
      - Individuals
        - A-B (Folder 4)
        - C-G (Folder 5)
        - H-M (Folder 6)
        - N-S (Folder 7)
        - T-Z (Folder 8)
      - State organization (Folder 9)
    - Michigan (Box 149)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Anonymous (Folder 2)
      - Cities - Detroit (Folder 3)
      - State organization (Folder 4)
    - Minnesota
      - General (Folder 5)
      - State organization (Folder 6)
    - Mississippi
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Anonymous (Folder 8)
      - State organization (Folder 9)
    - Missouri
      - General (Folder 10)
      - Anonymous (Folder 11)
      - State organization (Folder 12)
    - Montana (Box 150)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Anonymous (Folder 2)
      - State organization (Folder 3)
    - Nebraska
      - General (Folder 4)
      - State organization (Folder 5)
    - Nevada
      - General (Folder 6)
      - State organization (Folder 7)
    - New Hampshire
      - General (Folder 8)
      - State organization (Folder 9)
    - New Jersey
      - Anonymous (Folder 10)
      - Cities
        - Bayonne (Folder 11)
        - Bloomfield (Folder 12)
        - Cranford (Folder 13)
        - East Orange (Folder 14)
        - Elizabeth (Folder 15)
        - Englewood (Folder 16)
        - Glen Ridge (Folder 17)
        - Hackensack (Folder 18)
        - Hoboken (Folder 19)
        - Jersey City (Folder 20)
        - Leonia (Box 151, Folder 1)
        - Madison (Folder 2)
        - Maplewood (Folder 3)
        - Montclair (Folder 4)
        - Moorestown (Folder 5)
        - Morristown (Folder 6)
        - New Brunswick (Folder 7)
        - Newark
          - General (Folder 8)
          - Smith, Adele O. (Folder 9)
        - Orange (Folder 10)
        - Passaic (Folder 11)
        - Paterson (Folder 12)
        - Plainfield (Folder 13)
        - Princeton (Folder 14)
        - Rahway (Box 152, Folder 1)
        - Red Bank (Folder 2)
        - Ridgewood (Folder 3)
        - South Orange (Folder 4)
        - Summit (Folder 5)
        - Tenafly (Folder 6)
        - Trenton (Folder 7)
        - Upper Montclair (Folder 8)
        - West Orange (Folder 9)
        - Westfield (Folder 10)
      - Individuals (Folder 11-14)
      - Individuals (Box 153, Folder 1-5)
      - State organization (Folder 6)
      - State organization (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - New Mexico
      - General (Folder 2)
      - State organization (Folder 3)
    - New York
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Anonymous (Folder 5)
      - Cities/Burroughs/Counties
        - Albany (Folder 6)
        - Bronxville (Folder 7)
        - Buffalo (Box 155, Folder 1)
        - Hastings-on-Hudson (Folder 2)
        - Larchmont (Folder 3)
        - Long Island
          - Elmhurst (Folder 4)
          - Far Rockway (Folder 5)
          - Flushing (Folder 6)